WestConn Serials and Publications Catalogs, Yearbooks, View Books, Registration Booklets and Academic Journals RG 8.1
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Convocation, Commencement, and Other Programs
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1983; 53303 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1984; 38113 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1985; 38112 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1986; 38111 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1987; 38110 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1988; 38109 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1989; 38108 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1990; 38107 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1991; 38106 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1992; 38105 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1993; 38104 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1994; 38103 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1995; 38102 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1996; 38101 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1997; 38100 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1998; 38099 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 1999; 38098 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2000; 38097 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2001; 38096 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2002; 38094 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2003; 38092 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2004; 38091 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2005; 38090 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2017 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Honors Convocation Programs, 2018 (Box 34, Folder 30)